conservativeintel.com 2014-11-24

# Privacy Policy » Conservative Intelligence Briefing

Your privacy is critically important to us.

The Conservative Intelligence Briefing (also known as http://conservativeintel.com) has a few fundamental principles about privacy and the information we collect.

Conservative Intelligence Briefing will not ask you for personal information unless it is truly necessary;

Conservative Intelligence Briefing will not share your personal information with anyone except as required in order to comply with the law, develop our products, or protect our rights (as further discussed below);

Conservative Intelligence Briefing will utilize safe, secure technology to protect your personally identifiable information; and

You retain copyright and any other rights you already hold in Content, which you may submit, post or display through http://www.conservativeintel.com.

Below is our privacy policy, which incorporates these goals.

Conservative Intelligence Briefing operates a website at http://www.conservativeintel.com. It is Conservative Intelligence Briefing’s policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our website.

Website Visitors

Like most website operators, Conservative Intelligence Briefing collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Conservative Intelligence Briefing’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how Conservative Intelligence Briefing’s visitors use its website. From time to time, Conservative Intelligence Briefing may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

Conservative Intelligence Briefing also collects potentially personally identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses. Conservative Intelligence Briefing does not use such information to identify its visitors, however, and does not disclose such information, other than under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally identifying information, as described below.

Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information

Conservative Intelligence Briefing has created these web pages for your personal information and education. However, you are only authorized to access this website or to use the materials contained in the site if you agree to abide by all applicable laws, which constitutes an Agreement between you and Conservative Intelligence Briefing, Inc.

Opt-Out Policy

Conservative Intelligence Briefing offers its visitors and customers a means to choose how we may use information provided. If, at any time after registering for information or ordering services at http://www.conservativeintel.com , you change your mind about receiving information from us or about sharing your information with third parties, simply send as a request at info@conservativeintel.com .

Aggregated Statistics

Conservative Intelligence Briefing may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. Conservative Intelligence Briefing may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, Conservative Intelligence Briefing does not disclose personally identifying information other than as described below.

Protection of Certain Personally Identifying Information

Conservative Intelligence Briefing discloses potentially personally identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on Conservative Intelligence Briefing’s behalf or to provide services available at Conservative Intelligence Briefing’s websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country. By using Conservative Intelligence Briefing’s website, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. Conservative Intelligence Briefing will not rent or sell potentially personally identifying and personally identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, Conservative Intelligence Briefing discloses potentially personally identifying and personally-identifying information only when required to do so by law, or when Conservative Intelligence Briefing believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Conservative Intelligence Briefing, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of http://www.asgroupinc.com / and have supplied your email address, Conservative Intelligence Briefing may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with updates on Conservative Intelligence Briefing and our products. We primarily use our various email lists, social media profiles and product blogs to communicate this type of information, so we expect to keep this type of email to a minimum. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. Conservative Intelligence Briefing takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally identifying and personally identifying information.

Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Conservative Intelligence Briefing reserves the right to use cookies to help Conservative Intelligence Briefing identify and track visitors, their usage of Conservative Intelligence Briefing website, and their website access preferences. Conservative Intelligence Briefing visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using Conservative Intelligence Briefing’s websites, with the drawback that certain features of Conservative Intelligence Briefing’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

Reprint and Forward Policy

Subscribers may reprint or forward conservativeintel.com information and newsletters, in whole or part, with appropriate citation [“source: conservativeintel.com”] in accordance with “fair use” rules.

Third Party Websites

Conservative Intelligence Briefing uses third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, emails, address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. Conservative Intelligence Briefing is not responsible for the privacy practices of other websites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave iwvoice.org/and to read the privacy statements of each and every website to learn how such website collects and uses personally identifiable information.

Notice and takedown policy

Conservative Intelligence Briefing respects the Intellectual Property Rights of third parties. Pursuant to the Digital Millennium Copyright Act, 17 U.S.C. §512(c)(3), if you believe that your content has been copied in a way that constitutes trademark and/or copyright infringement, please inform use IMMEDIATELY, by stating the following:

Your contact details.  
A description of the content.  
The website address (URL) where the content is, or alternatively, the date when it was uploaded.  
An explanation of why the content should not be on www.conservativeintel.com .  
A statement that, under penalty of perjury, you are the owner of the Intellectual Property Rights or are authorized to act for the owner of the Intellectual Property Rights in the content.

The process for handling requests to remove content from www.conservativeintel.com as follows:

You will be notified as soon as possible of our receipt of your email; usually within two (2) days;  
The content will be removed as soon as possible.  
Conservative Intelligence Briefing will retain the email stating that you are the owner of the Intellectual Property Rights of said content or the representative and why the item should be removed.  
If you are identified as selling unauthorized goods, Conservative Intelligence Briefing reserves the right to disclose your identity and contact information, including any aliases or email address(es) that you may have previously used, upon request of the trademark and/or copyright owner, and to assist in any prosecution. This disclosure may be made without notice to you.

Website Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, Conservative Intelligence Briefing reserves the right to modify, amend, or alter its Privacy Policy from time to time. Conservative Intelligence Briefing encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.

DATED: 12 May 2011

comments
